gameadvert.com 2014-06-17

# Game Advert

This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by GameAdvert.com or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies. In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post separate privacy notices to describe how particular services process personal information, which are accessible from the navigation bar to the left of this notice. 

**Choices for personal information**   
When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.   
You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case our lead collective may not be able to provide those services to you. 

**Information security**   
We restrict access to personal information to gameadvert.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**Accessing and updating personal information**   
When you use gameadvert.com services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes.   
We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required.   
In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services. 

**Cookies**   
When viewing advertisements shown via the GameAdvert service, you may receive and transmit web cookies. If you would not like to receive and transmit such cookies, you may disable cookies for our site or sites in general within your web browser. 

**Changes to this policy**   
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. 

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site.   
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.   
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.   
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
